leaguesafe.com 2016-04-16

# LeagueSafe | The online solution for your fantasy sports entry fees

_Effective Date: July 7, 2011_

**LeagueSafe.com Privacy Policy**

LeagueSafe has created this privacy statement to help you (hereafter, "Members") understand the ways in which Members' personal information is gathered and used. At LeagueSafe, we recognize the importance of the confidentiality of the information we receive. This statement describes the information Members provide to LeagueSafe, LLC including our affiliates, partners, and agencies (collectively, "LeagueSafe"). This privacy policy outlines the manner in which we collect information, how we use it, and any circumstances in which we may disclose it. By accepting the privacy policy and Terms of Service during registration, Members expressly consent to LeagueSafe's use and disclosure of Member's personal information as described in the Privacy Statement. If this document is updated, Members are notified on their Member Home Page for 30 days after the revision has taken effect.

**Information Collection**

LeagueSafe requests only the information needed to administer our business, and to provide customers with products and services. LeagueSafe will not give, sell, rent, or share this information to other parties, except as described in this privacy policy.

**How We Gather Your Personal Information**

When Members visit the LeagueSafe site, we collect standard web logging information, such as Members' browser type, IP address, and a record of the pages Members access. 

When Members choose to register for the LeagueSafe Membership, they are asked to provide their name, address, email and other similar information. Financial information that is used for transaction processing, such as credit card information and/or bank information, is not stored by LeagueSafe. In order to comply with federal and state laws, banking regulations, and other guidelines to minimize risk and authenticate Member identity, Members may be required to offer additional information in order to verify identity or address. This may include Members' social security number or other personal information. LeagueSafe may also obtain information about Members from third parties such as identity verification services. LeagueSafe interacts with its Members via surveys and other means, and in these processes, information may be collected.

**Session Information**

LeagueSafe gathers IP addresses, browser types, and session information in order to administer the site, improve performance, and evaluate Member trends. The information is gathered and aggregated for broad analysis, and is stored for less than three years from the date collected.

**How We Use Cookies**

In many parts of the LeagueSafe website, "cookies" are placed on Members' computer. These help LeagueSafe provide an improved user experience in many situations. Many cookies are used only during a Member's contiguous session; others may expire in 24 hours. Many browsers have controls that limit the use of cookies.

**Customer Service Correspondence**

Correspondence with Members, including emails and faxes, may be retained. We retain these records in order to improve customer service, investigate possible fraud or criminal activities, monitor violations of LeagueSafe's Terms of Service, and to otherwise protect LeagueSafe's legal interests.

**Information Sharing**

LeagueSafe will not give, sell, rent, or share this information to other parties for their marketing purposes. In an effort to maintain validate the authenticity of each Member transaction, LeagueSafe may validate personal information Members provide, or request additional information from credit bureaus or other third parties, to assist us in establishing and authenticating a Member's account, and verifying the accuracy of the information that Members provide. Information obtained from third parties and linked with your personal information is safeguarded by confidentiality agreements and to the extent required by law.

When LeagueSafe Members sign up for a third-party service, we share only the contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide such services. Third parties are not authorized to use personal information except for the purpose of providing those services. Otherwise, LeagueSafe will not share or give Members' personal information to others unless in the rare case that LeagueSafe believes it is necessary to cooperate with regulators or law enforcement authorities or similar legal request including the protection of our rights or the rights of others. If a Member objects to personal information being transferred or used as described in this Privacy Statement, please do not register to use the LeagueSafe service or use this website.

Members may choose to opt into research studies offered by LeagueSafe, the Fantasy Sports Trade Association, or other non-commercial groups. Those who choose to opt-into these studies are authorizing LeagueSafe to provide the personal information needed for the study. This opt-in can be changed any time by changing your Member profile. 

**Links**

The LeagueSafe site may contain links to other sites, including links left by other Members in your league, on the league message board. Message board entries are not monitored by LeagueSafe. Any links posted on the message board are wholly the responsibility of the Member who posted them. LeagueSafe is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our Member to be aware when they leave our site to read the privacy statements of each website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to the Member experience at the LeagueSafe website.

**Data Access and Security**

Nearly all of the LeagueSafe web site runs under secure web protocols. The secure protected area of the LeagueSafe service may allow our customers, using a unique username and password, to access account information and transaction reporting, and to initiate or process transactions directly from the Website. LeagueSafe does not store Member's personal financial information.

We make reasonable efforts to ensure security on our systems. Despite our efforts, we cannot guarantee that personal information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed by breach of our administrative, managerial and technical safeguards. If a Member believes that to have been involved in an unauthorized transaction, contact LeagueSafe by sending an email to customerservice@leaguesafe.com.

If LeagueSafe learns of a security systems breach we may attempt to notify affected Members electronically so they can take appropriate protective steps. By using the LeagueSafe service, Members agree that LeagueSafe may communicate with Members electronically. LeagueSafe may post a notice on this Website if a security breach occurs. If this happens, Members will need a web browser enabling Members to view the LeagueSafe.com website. LeagueSafe may also send Members an email at the email address you have provided to us. Depending on where each Member lives, Members may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. To receive free written notice of a security breach (or to withdraw your consent from receiving electronic notice of a security breach) Members should notify us at customerservice@leaguesafe.com. 

**International Use**

As described in the LeagueSafe Terms of Service, LeagueSafe is available only to residents of the United States. By using the LeagueSafe service, Members expressly consent to the transfer and processing of personal information in the United States and elsewhere as LeagueSafe deems necessary to provide the LeagueSafe service. LeagueSafe strives to meet the laws and practices of the United States. Residents from other countries should not use the service, and should not expect that laws and practices from their country will be adhered to.

**Merger or Sale**

In the event of a change of ownership control over LeagueSafe, information collected by LeagueSafe will be treated as an asset, and may be transferred except to the extent the law may prohibit such transfers.

**Notification of Changes**

This document may change occasionally. When changes are made we will revise the effective date on the privacy policy. In the event that a change may be materially less restrictive on our use or disclosure of personal information, notification of the change will be made on Members' league home page for 30 days. A Member's continued use of the LeagueSafe web site and services constitutes an agreement to this privacy statement.

**Contacting LeagueSafe**

Any Member with a question or concern regarding the LeagueSafe service should contact LeagueSafe at [customerservice@leaguesafe.com ](mailto:customerservice@leaguesafe.com) . In the event that a Member remains unable to resolve his/her concerns, LeagueSafe is committed to cooperating to achieve a proper resolution.
